<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mehti Musayev</title>
    <link>https://musayev.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mehti Musayev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 00:30:10 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://musayev.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my blog!</title>
      <link>https://musayev.me/posts/my-first-post.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 00:30:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://musayev.me/posts/my-first-post.md/</guid>
      <description>I will try to keep this blog alive and put everything related to my studies, work and life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://musayev.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://musayev.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! My name is Mehti Musayev.&#xA;I was born in the last year of the Soviet Union and raised in Saint Petersburg, Russia, in a highly educated family.&#xA;I come from a multi-ethnic, multi-faith background, and I do not tolerate any form of xenophobia, nazism, or racism. Alongside my technical education, I also studied music and graduated as a cellist and pianist.&#xA;In my free time, I enjoy traveling, table tennis (ping pong), tennis, badminton, cycling, swimming, surfing, and snowboarding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum vitae</title>
      <link>https://musayev.me/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://musayev.me/cv/</guid>
      <description>Short CV Link to heading Professional Experience Link to heading (Tech) Lead AI Engineer (Data and AI) - OneClickLCA Ltd. (Finland), May 2024 – Present Senior AI Engineer (Data and AI) - OneClickLCA Ltd. (Finland), Aug 2023 – May 2024 AI Engineer - Symbio Finland Oy, 2021 – 2024 Lead ML Engineer (R&amp;amp;D) - Dash Energy Ltd. (USA), Nov 2021 – Dec 2022 (Contract) AI Engineer - Silo AI Oy (Finland), Jan 2021 – Aug 2021 ML Consultant - CGI Suomi Oy, May 2019 – Jan 2021 Education Link to heading Master of Science (Machine Learning, Data Science and AI) - Aalto University (Finland), Aug 2021 – Dec 2025 Bachelor of Science (Computer Science and Mathematics) - St.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donation</title>
      <link>https://musayev.me/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://musayev.me/donate/</guid>
      <description>If you like my projects, work or just want to buy me a coffee, feel free to use:&#xA;BTC: bc1q4nmnf8xa9a2uymt25gph9k6zel6l7n08dv5w9n&#xA;ETH: 0x6F1f8A9C39492e1C3aC3F3e23Bc4ff73cbb8Ff3C&#xA;ADA: Ae2tdPwUPEZLaRicJAQoTmkZGrzd3mme8vMnbHnmH6G8u7wsPhjQtJuckvt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://musayev.me/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://musayev.me/projects/</guid>
      <description>During my career I have been collaborating into limited number of open source and industrial projects.&#xA;My volunteer work for open source community started in 2016 when I was using several projects at work. In the following list one can find all open source and industrial projects where I am currently/used to be represented as a collaborator/team member:&#xA;Open source projects:&#xA;RedBaron baron yapf (owned by Google) ELFI (owned by Aalto University, Finland) Industrial projects:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
